<?xml version="1.0"?>
<JavaQuestions>
<MQuestion>
<question>
Which of the following statements is correct?
</question>
<answer>
2
</answer>
<choices>
A class in Java can extend one or more classes
A class in Java can extend one class and implement one or more interfaces
A class in Java can extend one interface and implement one or two classes
A class in Java can extend one class and implement one interface
</choices>
</MQuestion>
<TFQuestion>
<question>
You cannot override the toString() method in any class you create.
</question>
<answer>
False
</answer>
</TFQuestion>
<TFQuestion>
<answer>
false
</answer>
<question>
You can create an abstract class object using the new operator.
</question>
</TFQuestion>
<TFQuestion>
<question>
Superclasses can contain abstract methods.
</question>
<answer>
true
</answer>
</TFQuestion>
<MQuestion>
<question>
What is the result of compiling the following code?  

public class Test {  
       public static void main ( String[] args) {  
            int value; 
            value = value + 1;  
            System.out.println(" The value is : " + value);  
       }  
}
</question>
<choices>
Compile and runs with no output
Does not compile
Compiles and runs printing out "The value is 1"
Compiles but generates run time error
</choices>
<answer>
2
</answer>
</MQuestion>
<MQuestion>
<question>
The difference between an object and a class is
</question>
<choices>
A class is a blueprint of an object and an object reserves memory for variables based on the class blueprint
Nothing; they are both the same
An object is a blueprint of an object and a class reserves memory for variables based on the object blueprint
A class and an object both serve as templates to all java objects
</choices>
<answer>
1
</answer>
</MQuestion>
<MQuestion>
<question>
In Java, the concept of keeping data private is known as _______.
</question>
<choices>
polymorphism
information hiding
data deception
concealing fields
</choices>
<answer>
2
</answer>
</MQuestion>
<MQuestion>
<question>
A superclass can also be called a _______.
</question>
<choices>
child class
subclass
derived class
base class
</choices>
<answer>
4
</answer>
</MQuestion>
<TFQuestion>
<question>
All method declarations contain arguments.
</question>
<answer>
false
</answer>
</TFQuestion>
<MQuestion>
<question>
Which is true about an anonymous inner class?
</question>
<choices>
It can extend exactly one class and implement exactly one interface.
It can extend exactly one class and can implement multiple inerfaces.
It can extend exactly one class or implement exactly one interface.
It can implement mulitple interfaces regardless of whether it also extends a class.
It can implement multiple interfaces if it does not extends a class.
</choices>
<answer>
3
</answer>
</MQuestion>
<TFQuestion>
<question>
A constructor of a class can receive parameters.
</question>
<answer>
True
</answer>
</TFQuestion>
</JavaQuestions>